A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, DNA, Series G FA342
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Notebooks, 1; 3.2 Cubic Feet
  - Notebooks: Domestic Policy, Education (vol. VII) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Tab 8 Federal Aid to Education Tab 9 Commission on the Quality and Relevance of American Education - NAR proposal of organization. Tab 10-11 Federal Policy for Higher Education Tab 12 Department of Education Tab 13-14 Ghetto Schools Tab 15 National Educational Information System Tab 16 National Scholarship Plan Tab 17-18 Conant Proposal Critique Tab 19-20 NAR-Gardner Meeting, May 4
  - Notebooks: Federal System and Government Organization (vol. VIII) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Tab 1-8 General Tab 9-14 New System for Federal Aid Distribution Tab 15-16 Office of Executive Management Tab 17-18 Federal-State-Local Liaison Unit Tab 19-24 The Presidency Tab 25-26 New Federal Departments: Education and Human Rights Tab 27 Executive-Judicial Relationships Tab 28 Supreme Court Vacancy Tab 29 Post Office Corporation
  - Notebooks: Health (vol. IX) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Tab 1-5 General Tab 6-7 Hospital Cost Control Tab 8 Program for Low-Income Areas Tab 9 Health Manpower Tab 10 Mentally Retarded Tab 11 Mental Illness Tab 12 Emergency Medical Plan Tab 13 Nursing Homes Tab 14 Alcoholism
  - Notebooks: Jobs (vol. X) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Tab 1-9 General Tab 10-14 Manpower Program Reform Tab 15 Public Sector Jobs Tab 16 Federal Aid to Ghetto Businesses Tab 17 Improving Job Placement Information Tab 18 Post-Vietnam Job Planning Tab 19 "Full Opportunity Act"
  - Notebooks: Welfare (vol. XI) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Tab 1-8 General Tab 9-10 Negative Income Tax Tab 11 Aid to Dependent Children Tab 12 Child Welfare Tab 13-17 Hunger and Food Distribution Tab 18-19 Community Self-Help Corporation Tab 20-21 Office of Economic Opportunity
  - Notebooks: Youth (vol. XII) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Tab 1-3 General Tab 4 Youth Participation & Programs Tab 5-12 Selective Service Reform Tab 13 Draft Board Reorganization Tab 14-18 18-year-old Vote Tab 19-20 Student Protest and Dissent
  - Notebooks: Miscellaneous (vol. XIII) (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Tab 1 American Indian Tab 2-4 Arts Tab 5 Consumer Protection Tab 6 Government Sale of Land Tab 7-15 "New Leadership" Tab 16-17 Recreation Tab 18 Science Tab 19-21 Transportation
  - Notebooks: Nixon on Civil Rights (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Briefing book, which includes a general position paper on civil rights record. Includes memos on Nixon's major weaknesses and suggest possible means for exploiting them. Prepared by Answer Desk, Graham T.T. Molitor, Director.
    I Southern Strategy II Open Housing III Busing IV Riots V Rebuilding the Ghetto VI General Position Paper
  - Notebooks: Answer Desk Profile on Richard Nixon (Box 5, Folder 31)
    I The Loser Image II The Political Image: Tricky Dick
  - Notebooks: Answer Desk Profile on Richard Nixon (Box 5, Folder 32)
    III Personality: The Unstable Man IV Everybody on Nixon V Campaign Style
  - Notebooks: Answer Desk Profile on Richard Nixon (Box 5, Folder 33)
    VI Nixon: Unqualified for President VII Appendix VIII Index of Cross References
  - Notebooks: Index to DNA Research, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Notebooks: Candidate Positions (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Published brochures, statements, speeches, press releases, internal memoranda on the positions held on national issues by the major candidates for Presidency in 1968: Hubert Humphrey, Robert Kennedy, Ronald Reagan, Richard Nixon.
  - Notebooks: Candidate Positions (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Notebooks: Candidate Positions (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Notebooks: Candidate Positions (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Notebooks: Candidate Positions (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Notebooks: Recommended NAR Position Statements (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Notebooks: Recommended NAR Position Statements (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Notebooks: NAR Speeches, Questions and Answers (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Notebooks: NAR Speeches, Questions and Answers (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Notebooks: NAR Speeches, Questions and Answers (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Notebooks: NAR Meeting, May 22, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Position notebook for NAR, used in meeting with Michigan Republican Party Delegates.
  - Notebooks: NAR Meeting, May 22, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Notebooks: 1960 Republican Platform (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Notebooks: 1964 Republican Platform (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Notebooks: 1964 Republican Platform (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Notebooks: 1964 Republican Platform (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Notebooks: Platform Comparisons (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    Policy papers prepared for the Republican Governors Policy Committee, as a result of their decision to develop background material on problems in foreign policy.
    Book 1 - data on individual countries Tab 1 Introductory Letter to Governor Chafee, June 13, 1968 Tab 2 United Kingdom Tab 3 France Tab 4 Germany Tab 5 Berlin Tab 6 Eastern Europe
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    Book 1 - data on individual countries Tab 7 Union of Soviet Socialist Republics Tab 8 Japan Tab 9 Vietnam
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    Book 2 - data on regional and functional problems Tab 10 The Middle East Tab 11 South Asia Tab 12 Latin America Tab 13 European Economic Community Tab 14 North Atlantic Treaty Organization
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    Book 2 - data on regional and functional problems Tab 15 Defense Tab 16 United Nations Tab 17 Arms Control and Disarmament
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    Book 3 - economic studies Tab 18 Foreign Economic Policy Tab 19 Economic Aid
  - Notebooks: Republican Governors Association, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    Book 3 - economic studies Tab 20 East-West Trade Tab 21 Balance of Payments
- Files for the 1968 Campaign, 2; 5.6 Cubic Feet
  This material comprises supplementary documentation for the notebooks found in subseries 1. Boxes 17 to 21 of this subseries contain the original documents used for the notebooks that were disseminated among Governor Rockefeller's staff. Also noteworthy are the fact sheet files for each state visited by Governor Rockefeller, which contain pertinent information on the state. The majority of the material is correspondence and chronological files created during the running of a national campaign. Finally, there are also the organizational files for the DNA group.
  - Alsop, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 58)
    Copy of Alsop's "Washington Post" column, dated July 1, 1968.
  - Answer Desk (Box 9, Folder 59)
    Correspondence and memoranda from Richard Nathan and other DNA staff with the Answer Desk, an organization to collect information, headed by Graham Molitor.
  - Answer Desk - Appraisal of Candidate Research (Box 9, Folder 60)
    Report from Molitor and Answer Desk staff on the National Bipartisan Movement, Inc., which was also involved with issue information gathering.
  - Applicants (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Correspondence and staff memoranda on individuals recommended for employment with Definitive News Analysis.
  - Applicants - Active (Box 9, Folder 62)
    Correspondence with possible candidates for employment with Definitive News Analysis.
  - Apportionment of Delegates (Box 9, Folder 63)
    Report and analysis of delegates attending the 1968 Republican Convention.
  - Briefing Memos (Box 9, Folder 64)
    Copies of excerpts from NAR press conferences and DNA briefing memos on issues submitted to NAR.
  - Briefing Memos (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Briefing Memos (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Butler, William (Box 9, Folder 67)
    Memoranda with Butler on various economic issues.
  - Checklist (Box 10, Folder 68)
    Internal memoranda on areas of domestic policy to be addressed.
  - "Chicago Tribune," June 21, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    Editorial on NAR's political power in the Republican party.
  - Choate, Robert (Box 10, Folder 70)
    Memoranda with Choate on speech material, primarily of domestic issues.
  - Clipping Service (Box 10, Folder 71)
    Collection of press clippings, memoranda discussing the hiring of a professional service to track NAR in the news.
  - Consultants (Box 10, Folder 72)
    (empty folder)
  - Correspondence - Chronological File - April-June 1968 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence - Chronological File - April-June 1968 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence - Chronological File - April-June 1968 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence - Nathan, Richard P. (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence - Reubhausen, Oscar M. (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Diamond, Henry (Box 10, Folder 78)
    Memoranda with Diamond on NAR speech editing.
  - DNA - General Office Procedure (Box 10, Folder 79)
    Staff memoranda on office practices; phone directories of DNA staff.
  - Domestic Policy Papers List (Box 10, Folder 80)
    List of topics and issues being written for issue notebooks.
  - Domestic Research - Organization (Box 10, Folder 81)
    Lists of individuals to be sent domestic issues policy papers for review; list of individuals to be consulted on various domestic issues.
  - Domestic Research - Resumes (Box 10, Folder 82)
    Individual resumes of people hired to assist in formulating domestic policy papers.
  - Douglass, Robert (Box 10, Folder 83)
    Memoranda accompanying issues notebook sent to Douglass.
  - Douglass, Robert (Box 10, Folder 84)
    Rockefeller for President News - press releases from RFP sent to DNA office by Douglass, head of RFP.
  - Fact Sheets - Washington, D.C. (Box 11, Folder 85)
    Information summaries on Washington, D.C. and several states visited by NAR in the 1968 campaign. Includes statistical information and names of government officials.
  - Fact Sheets - Arkansas (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Fact Sheets - California, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Fact Sheets - Colorado (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Fact Sheets - Connecticut (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Fact Sheets - Delaware (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Fact Sheets - Florida (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Fact Sheets - Georgia (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Fact Sheets - Hawaii (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Fact Sheets - Idaho (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Fact Sheets - Illinois (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Fact Sheets - Indiana (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Fact Sheets - Iowa (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Fact Sheets - Kansas (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Fact Sheets - Kentucky (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Fact Sheets - Louisiana (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Fact Sheets - Maine (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Fact Sheets - Maryland (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Fact Sheets - Massachusetts (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Fact Sheets - Michigan (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Fact Sheets - Minnesota (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Fact Sheets - Missouri (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Fact Sheets - Montana (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Fact Sheets - Nebraska (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Fact Sheets - Nevada (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Fact Sheets - New Jersey (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Fact Sheets - New Mexico (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Fact Sheets - North Dakota (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Fact Sheets - Ohio (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Fact Sheets - Okalahoma (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Fact Sheets - Oregon (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Fact Sheets - Pennsylvania (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Fact Sheets - Rhode Island (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Fact Sheets - South Carolina (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Fact Sheets - South Dakota (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Fact Sheets - Tennessee (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Fact Sheets - Texas (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Fact Sheets - Utah (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Fact Sheets - Vermont (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Fact Sheets - Virginia (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Fact Sheets - Washington (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Fact Sheets - West Virginia (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Fact Sheets - Wisconsin (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Fact Sheets - Wyoming (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Fowler, Dennis (Box 12, Folder 129)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Fowler, primarily regarding statistical data.
  - "The Governor" (Box 12, Folder 130)
    Copies of memoranda forwarded to NAR for review.
  - Hanks, Nancy (Box 12, Folder 131)
    Correspondence and memoranda on various DNA and other campaign issues.
  - Hinman, George (Box 12, Folder 132)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Hinman.
  - Hoglund, Steve (Box 12, Folder 133)
    Correspondence with Hoglund, who sent a suggested position paper on violence.
  - Hughes, Emmet (Box 12, Folder 134)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Hughes on various political issues.
  - Hurd, Norman (Box 12, Folder 135)
    Notes from telephone conversation with Hurd on various issues.
  - Javits, Jacob (Box 12, Folder 136)
    Correspondence with the US Senator; press release from Senate Office of transcript of Javits press conference.
  - Keith, John (Box 12, Folder 137)
    Notes from meeting with Keith covering a variety of issues.
  - Kissinger, Henry (Box 12, Folder 138)
    Correspondence and memoranda on both domestic and foreign policy issues; suggestions offered by Kissinger on policy papers.
  - Kurzman, Stephen (Box 12, Folder 139)
    Memo from Kurzman offering additions and changes to policy paper on national leadership.
  - Liberty Lowdown (Box 12, Folder 140)
    Leaflet titled, "Nelson Rockefeller: Communist Agent."
  - Losee, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 141)
    Memo from Losee suggesting advertising strategy.
  - Lubell, Sam (Box 12, Folder 142)
    Memoranda and correspondence from Lubell, offering material on racial issues for NAR speech.
  - Lubell, Sam - Speech Material (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Lubell, Sam - Speech Material (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Lubell, Sam - Speech Material (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - McCurdy, Howard (Box 13, Folder 146)
    Correspondence and memoranda; draft policy paper on improving public communications policy.
  - Marshall, Alton (Box 13, Folder 147)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Marshall on political issues.
  - "Massive Rockefeller Record" (Box 13, Folder 148)
    Selected pages from updated version of the Rockefeller Record sent to DNA for dissemination to staff.
  - Material for Indian Statement (Box 13, Folder 149)
    Information collected in advance of NAR statement on American Indians.
  - Material for Press Club Speech (Box 13, Folder 150)
    Information collected in advance of NAR speech at the National Press Club, Washington, D.C.
  - Media Distribution Services - Invoices and Payments (Box 14, Folder 151)
    Organization used to disseminate NAR speeches.
  - Media Distribution Services - Invoices and Payments (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Media Distribution Services - Invoices and Payments (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Media Distribution Services - Mail Speech Operation (Box 14, Folder 154)
    Procedure to be followed in mailing out NAR speeches.
  - Media Distribution Services - Payment of Bills (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Meeting Summaries (Box 14, Folder 156)
    Typewritten notes and minutes of meetings NAR attended with various experts on issues.
  - Memos - Extras (Box 14, Folder 157)
    Duplicate copies of procedural memos.
  - Memos - Memo for the Record (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Memos - Memos to Researchers (Box 15, Folder 159)
    Staff memos to DNA researchers.
  - Memos - Originals (Box 15, Folder 160)
    Procedural memos distributed to staff.
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Mitchell, Donna (Box 15, Folder 162)
    Correspondence and memoranda.
  - Moore, Tom (Box 15, Folder 163)
    Speech material.
  - Morrow, Hugh (Box 15, Folder 164)
    Correspondence and memoranda regarding changes in positions.
  - NAR Accomplishments (Box 15, Folder 165)
    Summary of NAR accomplishments, generally and in New York State.
  - NAR Itinerary (Box 15, Folder 166)
    Schedule for the week prior to the Republican National Convention.
  - NAR Questions and Answers (Box 15, Folder 167)
    Printed responses posed to NAR by various newspapers.
  - NAR Statements on Other Candidates (Box 15, Folder 168)
    Selections of press conferences where NAR was asked of impressions and actions of other presidential candidates.
  - NAR Statements on Other Candidates (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Nevin, David (Box 15, Folder 170)
    Correspondence and memoranda with Nevin; material on the poor.
  - News Conferences, Non-Foreign (Box 16, Folder 171)
    Copies of transcripts of NAR appearances, press conferences, questions relating to domestic issues.
  - News Conferences, Non-Foreign (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - News Conferences, Non-Foreign (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Night Help (Box 16, Folder 174)
    Time sheets for DNA staff who helped to assemble notebooks.
  - Night Help (Box 16, Folder 175)
  - Notebook Originals - Aged (Box 17, Folder 176)
    Drafts and original documents that were accumulated and organized into issue notebooks for the presidential campaign.
    Related Archival Materials note
    See boxes 1-8.
  - Notebook Originals - Agriculture (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Notebook Originals - Agriculture - Consultants (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Notebook Originals - Agriculture - "Elements of a Farm Statement" (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Notebook Originals - Agriculture - Meeting with Oren Staley, President of the National Farmers Organization, July 2, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Notebook Originals - Agriculture - Policy (Box 17, Folder 181)
  - Notebook Originals - Air and Water Pollution (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Notebook Originals - Air Safety (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - Notebook Originals - Arts (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Notebook Originals - The Budget (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Notebook Originals - Civil Disorders (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Notebook Originals - Civil Rights (Box 17, Folder 187)
  - Notebook Originals - Community Development Corporation (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Notebook Originals - Community Service (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Notebook Originals - Conservation and Recreation (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Notebook Originals - Consumer Protection (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Administration of Justice (Box 17, Folder 192)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Delinquency, and Administration of Justice (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Gun Control (Box 17, Folder 194)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Merger of Federal Crime Control Agencies (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Omnibus Crime Bill (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - Notebook Originals - Crime - Statement, June 28, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 197)
  - Notebook Originals - D.C. Home Rule (Box 18, Folder 198)
  - Notebook Originals - The Draft, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 199)
  - Notebook Originals - The Draft - Lubell Notes (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - Notebook Originals - Economy (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Notebook Originals - Economy - Detroit Speech (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Notebook Originals - Economy - Issues (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Notebook Originals - Economy - Post-Vietnam Economic Policy (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Notebook Originals - Economy - Refutation of "Barron's" Article (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Notebook Originals - Education (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Notebook Originals - Education - Department of Education (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Notebook Originals - Education - Saunders Materials (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Notebook Originals - Eighteen-year-old Vote (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Notebook Originals - Equal Opportunity (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Notebook Originals - Executive Office of the President (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Notebook Originals - Federalism (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Notebook Originals - Food Stamp Programs (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Notebook Originals - Gardner, John - Letter (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Notebook Originals - Government Organization (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Notebook Originals - Health (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Notebook Originals - Housing, Urban Renewal, Model Cities (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Notebook Originals - Hunger (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Notebook Originals - Ideas and Suggestions (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Notebook Originals - Intergovernmental Relations (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Notebook Originals - Jobs (Box 19, Folder 221)
  - Notebook Originals - Kelso, Economic Opportunity for the Disadvantaged (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Notebook Originals - Kennedy, Robert (Box 19, Folder 223)
    Memoranda on RFK decision to tap the phone of Martin Luther King, Jr.
  - Notebook Originals - Labor Management (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Notebook Originals - Manpower (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Notebook Originals - Manpower Report (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Notebook Originals - Michigan Questions (Box 19, Folder 227)
    First draft.
  - Notebook Originals - Narcotics Addiction (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Notebook Originals - National Community Service (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Notebook Originals - National Federation of Independent Businesses (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Notebook Originals - Nixon Profile (Box 20, Folder 231)
  - Notebook Originals - Nixon Profile (Box 20, Folder 232)
  - Notebook Originals - Nixon Profile (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Notebook Originals - Population - Family Planning (Box 20, Folder 234)
  - Notebook Originals - President's Commission on Income Maintenance Programs (Box 20, Folder 235)
  - Notebook Originals - Racial Problems in Schools (Box 20, Folder 236)
  - Notebook Originals - "Rebuilding Our Cities" (Box 20, Folder 237)
  - Notebook Originals - Resurrection City (Box 20, Folder 238)
  - Notebook Originals - Revenue Bonds (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - Notebook Originals - Science (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Notebook Originals - Small Business (Box 20, Folder 241)
  - Notebook Originals - Social Security (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Notebook Originals - Space (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Notebook Originals - State-Local Relationships (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - Notebook Originals - Taxation (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Notebook Originals - Taxation - Tax Policy and Children Allowances (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Notebook Originals - Tax Policies (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Notebook Originals - Urban Development Corporation (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Notebook Originals - Veterans (Box 21, Folder 249)
  - Notebook Originals - Welfare - Poverty (Box 21, Folder 250)
  - Notebook Originals - Youth (Box 21, Folder 251)
  - Overtime (Box 21, Folder 252)
    Time sheets for DNA staff.
  - Persico, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 253)
    Correspondence and memoranda on speech topics.
  - Petition to Support Rockefeller (Box 21, Folder 254)
    Campaign materials.
  - Platform (Box 21, Folder 255)
    1968 Republican Party Platform.
  - Press Conferences/Q&A (Box 21, Folder 256)
    Copies of transcripts of NAR press conferences and reporter question and answer sessions.
  - Press Conferences/Q&A (Box 21, Folder 257)
  - Press Conferences/Q&A (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - Press Conferences/Q&A (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Press Statements (Box 22, Folder 260)
    Summary memoranda on press releases prepared by DNA staff.
  - Price, Donald (Box 22, Folder 261)
    Notes of conversation.
  - Proposed "Campaign Booklet" (Box 22, Folder 262)
    Suggested brochure for use in the Rockefeller for President campaign (sample of brochure).
  - Record of Who's Who with Gray Books (Box 22, Folder 263)
    List of individuals receiving issue notebooks.
  - Rockefeller for President (Box 22, Folder 264)
    Correspondence and memoranda with the RFP organization.
  - Rockefeller on the Issues, Domestic (Box 22, Folder 265)
    Policy memos on domestic issues prepared by DNA staff.
  - Rodriguez, Justine (Box 22, Folder 266)
    Paper submitted on "A Proud and Prosperous People" and welfare issues.
  - Reubhausen, Oscar (Box 22, Folder 267)
    Correspondence and memoranda on various issues.
  - Spanish-Americans (Box 22, Folder 268)
    Memo to DNA staff for ideas on "Themes for Use with Mexican-Americans."
  - Speech Drafts (Box 22, Folder 269)
    List, proposals, guidelines for speeches drafted by DNA Staff.
  - Statement on American Indian (Box 22, Folder 270)